{
	"name":"Basic Scrum Guides Quiz",
	"questions":[
		{
			"question":"Does scrum have rules, or just guidelines?",
			"answers":[
				"Scrum has a few simple rules",
				"Scrum has guidelines only, no rules at all."
			],
			"correct":"0"
		},
		{
			"question":"When should a retrospective meeting be held?",
			"answers":[
				"At the end of each sprint, after the sprint review meeting",
				"At the end of each sprint, before the sprint review meeting",
				"Every now and then, when the team wants to improve",
				"Only at the end of a project"
			],
			"correct":"1"
		},
				{
			"question":"Which one of the following is not a Scrum role?",
			"answers":[
				"Product Owner",
				"Scrum Master",
                "Product Manager",
                "Team"
			],
			"correct":"2"
		},
		{
			"question":"Which of the following meeting is not part of Scrum?",
			"answers":[
				"Product review meeting",
				"Sprint review meeting",
                "Sprint planning meeting",
                "Sprint retrospective meeting"
			],
			"correct":"0"
		},      
		{
			"question":"What is the duration of a sprint in Scrum?",
			"answers":[
				"4 weeks",
				"28-30 days",
                "Anything between 2 - 6 weeks",
                "30 days"
			],
			"correct":"2"
		},    
		{
			"question":"What is the goal of the Daily Scrum?",
			"answers":[
				"To ensure the team finishes the Sprint Backlog at the end of the Sprint",
				"To report progress to the ScrumMaster",
                "To answer the Three Questions",
                "To re-plan the work for the next day so the Sprint achieves the Sprint Goal"
			],
			"correct":"3"
		},    
		{
			"question":"The Product Backlog is",
			"answers":[
				"Unordered",
				"In delivery order",
                "In priority order",
                "In value and cost order"
			],
			"correct":"1"
		},    
		{
			"question":"The Product Backlog is",
			"answers":[
				"a list of requirements",
				"a list of Enabling Specifications",
                "a list of descriptions of product features and deliverables",
                "a roadmap"
			],
			"correct":"2"
		},      
		{
			"question":"Which best describes the relationship between the Product Owner and the Development/Delivery Team?",
			"answers":[
				"The PO defines the Product Backlog contents and the Developers provide constraints that the PO uses to properly order it",
				"The whole Scrum Team comes to a consensus on Product Backlog content",
                "The PO defines the ROI of each PBI and the Developers define cost, and the rest is just a mechanical reordering to optimize profit",
                "The PO and Developers define the Product Backlog together, but the PO has final say on the ordering and content"
			],
			"correct":"3"
		},     
		{
			"question":"Which of the following questions is not relevant for regular Scrum Meeting?",
			"answers":[
				"What have you done since the last Daily Scrum regarding this project?",
				"What will you do between now and the next Daily Scrum meeting regarding this project?",
                "Would you be able to finish your work on time?",
                "What impedes you from performing your work as effectively as possible?"
			],
			"correct":"2"
		}  		
	]
}